*我能把它称为家吗*
Can I call it home?
*你来时的路  和你回去的路*
The way you come, the way you go?
*只有我的时候我很孤单*
It's lonesome when it's only me.
第三季   第六集
指定
幸存者
这是谁
What are we looking at?
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
八岁的马特奥·奥雷利亚纳 他患有肾脏疾病
Eight-year-old Mateo Orellana, suffering from kidney disease.
两天前他的父母非法将他带过了边境
His parents brought him over the border illegally two nights ago.
翻 译   釉芭  Alyson
他目前正在厄尔巴索的急诊室接受透析治疗
He's currently receiving dialysis treatment at an ER in El Paso.
这个家庭希望能够进行移植手术
The family is hoping to procure a transplant.
各大报道中莫斯的那些支持者都是可预见的煽动者
The Moss campaign is predictably demagoguing on every cable channel.
翻 译   LNLZ   薛定谔的猫
他们对患病入侵者夺走了美国人健康的肾脏这件事强烈抗议
They're shrieking about illness invaders taking American kidneys.
美国人的健康肾脏  莫斯真的那么说
"American kidneys"? Moss really said that?
翻 译  Tang糖饼  Vicky
是菲尔·布伦顿说的  他是一个行尸走肉般的移民反对者
Phil Brunton, his cadaverous immigration troll.
- 肾脏移植进展怎么样  - 医院拒绝了手术
- What's the status of the transplant? - Hospital's refusing.
布伦顿声称艾斯组织应该突袭急诊室
With Brunton saying ICE should raid the ER
翻 译  DZNN
- 并驱逐整个家庭  - 死掉的孩子和他的家人
- and deport the entire family. - Dying kid and all.
- 我们可以强迫医院做手术吗  - 还不知道
- Can we force the hospital to do it? - Unclear.
- 并且这可能不是聪明的做法  - 哦 那好吧
- And possibly unwise. - Oh, here we go.
校 对   哎哟
你不会真的以为美国人民希望这个孩子去死吧
You can't honestly think the American people want this kid to die.
我们只有四周了  大多数公众的想法不是那么重要了
We're four weeks out. It doesn't matter what the public at large wants.
特 效   小螺号
重点是如何在我们需要笼络民心的州赢得选票
How does it poll in the states we need to win?
那就是中西部的工业城市和佛罗里达州
The industrial Midwest and Florida.
先生  我们不能什么都做  这个事件已经爆发了
We can't do nothing, sir. The story's already blowing up.
赛斯是对的   无所作为看起来太冷谈了
Seth's right. Inaction looks like indifference.
战况越加紧张  莫斯正利用这件事稳固民心
The race is tightening up. Moss is using this to secure his base.
我们永远也不会对他们出手的
We never had a shot at them anyway.
波特完全自由了  我们可以利用这件事作为契机去做一些事
Porter's in free fall. We can use this as a chance to do the right thing
并且剥夺他的民主党基本票源
and peel away at his Democratic base.
- 非裔美国人  性少数人群的选票  - 和拉丁美洲人的
- African Americans, the LGBTQ vote. - And Latinos.
对不起  我很困惑  现在你觉得我们应该采取措施了吗
I'm sorry, I'm confused. Now you think we should intervene?
你说服我的  亲爱的
You convinced me, sweetie.
我们需要进行一个实时调查  来确保我们是对的
But we'll have to do a snap poll, make sure we're right.
- 同时  把亚伦送到厄尔巴索  - 对他做什么
- And meanwhile, send Aaron to El Paso. - To do what?
要在他面前表现出一些担忧  使他参与竞选
To show some concern, be the face of the campaign.
这是一个没有意义的行动  我们没有机会取胜的
It's an empty-calorie photo op in a state we have no chance at winning.
不  这会给我们争取一些时间  这是一个好主意
No, it'll buy us time. It's a good idea.
上次的辩论后  莫斯一直在紧张的运作着
Moss is running nervous since the debate.
那么我们就去弄一些去看望肾病孩子的报道
So go get some free coverage visiting the sick kid.
这将迫使莫斯向昂贵的媒体市场砸入巨资
And we'll force Moss to pour money into an expensive media market
从而骗他进行防守
that we trick him into defending.
从而削弱他在我们已知领域争夺民心的能力
Depleting his ability to fight in areas we know are up for grabs.
我靠  你们太聪明了
Damn, you guys are good.
同时  我将与马尔斯联系
In the meantime, I'll reach out to Mars.
他将会开始为马特奥寻找合适的肾源  感谢大家
He'll start looking for transplant options for Mateo. Thank you, everyone.
先生 谢谢你
Thank you, sir.
这是合理使用致命武器
It was a justifiable use of deadly force.
我一再要求克劳福德放下他的武器
I repeatedly asked Crawford to put his weapon down.
我猜希特勒的崇拜者中的白人至上主义者
I guess Hitler-worshiping white supremacists
不喜欢接受有色人种的命令
don't like taking orders from people of color.
好吧如果能重来  我将会把市民留在车里
Okay, if I had to do it over, I would've left the civilian in the car,
但我需要伊莱告诉我是否
but I needed Eli to tell me whether...
如果你吼我一顿  我想我们都会感觉好些
I think we would both feel better if you just yelled at me.
汉娜  那样不会感觉好些的
That would not be pleasant, Hannah.
我了解这个是因为我刚刚被哈德利主管斥责
And I would know because I just received a rigorous ass-reaming
就是因为你的事
from Director Hadley over you.
我怎么了  揭露那些开发种族灭绝生物武器的
For what? Uncovering a highly-educated extremist hate group
高学历极端仇恨团体也是错的吗
who's developing genocidal bioweapons?
在美国土地上监视   然后杀害一名美国公民
For spying on, then killing, an American citizen on American soil.
这不是我们的工作  那是联邦调查局的工作
That's not what we do. That's the FBI's job.
他们做的很糟糕
Well, they're doing a piss-poor job of it.
他们在这个群体安插了眼线  但他们什么线索也没有
They had eyes on this group. They didn't have a clue.
你觉得他们会感激你做的事吗
Then they'll appreciate the treasure trove you have for them.
收拾你的文件  这里将由联邦调查局接管
Gather up your files. The FBI is taking over from here.
黛安娜  你不能把我从这件事踢出去
Dianne, you can't take me off this case.
这些话留着和副主管麦克米伦说吧  四点他等你汇报这件事
Take it up with Deputy Director McMillan. He's debriefing you at 4:00.
我和副主管麦克米伦的关系不是很好
Deputy Director McMillan and I don't have the greatest relationship.
滚出我的办公室  否则咱俩的关系也好不起来了
Get the hell out of my office or you'll be saying the same about me.
早上好  你看起来很惬意呀
Good morning. You look comfortable.
从这里开始工作很难
It's hard to work from here
尤其是当奥赛在塞纳河畔时
when the d'Orsay's on the bank of the Seine,
但这个地方有它的魅力
but this place has its charms.
如果你愿意  可以留下来  佩妮喜欢你在这里
You can stay if you want. Penny loves having you here.
你确定  用孩子的幸福诱惑我吗
You? Dangling your child's happiness as a carrot?
我也喜欢你在这儿
I enjoy you being here, too.
主席先生  法国文化专员和他的妻子已经到了
Sir, the French cultural attaché has arrived with his wife.
谢谢  拉塞尔
Thank you, Russell.
你愿意扮演这儿的女主人吗  他们一定想看到一些艺术品
Would you care to play hostess? They would like to see some art.
那我不就得挪窝了不是
That'd require me to move from this spot.
在我这  休息可是很珍贵的
Well, repose is a fleeting luxury here.
另外  我想不出比你更适合这项任务的人了
Besides, I can't think of anyone more suited to the task.
你要是这么说的话
When you put it that way...
我想我也可以赏脸陪陪他们
I suppose I could grace them with my company.
太棒了  拉塞尔一会儿就回来  谢谢你
Great. Russell will be back in moments. Thank you.
打扰了  我要取一个  罗琳去哪了
Sorry, I had to take a... Where's Lorraine?
- 我不知道  我以为她和你在一起  - 没有
- I don't know. I thought she was with you. - No.
- 我去找找看  - 好的
- I'll try and find her. - Okay.
好的  亚伦要去拜访一个将死的小男孩  所以我就长话短说
All right, Aaron has to go visit a dying boy, so I'll make this quick.
不要再发生关系了
No more fucking...
你们两个之间
each other.
- 什么  你告诉她的吗  - 不  你刚刚说的
- What? You told her? - No, you just did.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
在佛罗里达州我发现你在他的酒店房间外羞耻地踱步
When I caught you taking the walk of shame outside his hotel room in Florida,
你那充满负罪感  像车头灯一样深邃的大眼睛出卖了你
your big, guilty, deer-in-headlights eyes gave it away.
这是一场由酒精和危机推动的可怕的错误
Look, it was a crisis and alcohol-fueled terrible mistake
再也不会发生了
that will never happen again.
随便你  你们知道现在的一举一动都在监视下吗
Whatever. Do you know the microscope you're under?
你们不能再胡闹了
This cannot be monkey business as usual.
- 我不是那种人  - 希望你不是那种人
- I'm not that kind of guy. - Let's hope you're not anymore.
只要寡妇柯克曼还没准备好约会
As long as widow Kirkman is not ready to date,
你和伊莎贝尔的浪漫关系是我唯一的法宝了
this Aaronbel romance is all I've got.
这是我需要保护的一个非常有价值的商品
It is a very valuable commodity that I need to protect.
- 你不必保护它  - 她是对的
- You don't have to protect it - She's right.
民意调查显示女性喜欢伊莎贝尔
The polls show women love Isabel.
他们是这样的  他们也喜欢你  亚伦
They do. And they like you, too, Aaron.
但是如果他们发现你是华盛顿炮王的话  他们也会像对待过期的鱼一样对待你们
But they'll turn on you like week-old fish if they think that you'll bang anybody.
行吧  我真是在哪儿都不应该在这儿
This has been fun, but I need to be literally anywhere but here.
我得去德克萨斯州  原因我完全不清楚
I gotta go to Texas, for reasons I'm entirely unclear about.
我会给你发电子邮件
Well, I will email you talking points.
罗密欧  不要四处乱搞
And keep it in your pants, Romeo.
德克萨斯州  不是自愿的
Uh, Texas. Not my choice.
- 他们把你派去厄尔巴索吗  - 是的
- Are they sending you to El Paso? - Yeah.
- 这不是一个坏主意  - 就他妈是去作作秀
- Hmm. It's not a bad idea. - It's a fucking photo op.
这也是一种消除那些混蛋言论的方式
It's also a way to neutralize douchebags saying
他们说棕色人种是来索取我们的生命  自由和追求幸福的权利的
brown people are coming for your life, liberty and pursuit of happiness.
派国土安全部部长去处理
Well, send the secretary of Homeland Security.
不要那么明显地派我在我的家乡鼓动拉丁裔选民的支持
Don't send me on a transparent attempt to drum up Latino votes in my home state.
嘿  还有一个小男孩需要我们的帮助
Hey. There's also a little boy that needs our help.
- 也关注一下那件事  - 好的
- Try to focus on that. - Right.
- 我爱你  - 是的  我也爱你
- Te amo. - Yeah, I love you, too.
你们好  亲爱的新闻同事们  尽管问我吧
Greetings, my journalistic colleagues. Hit me.
关于德克萨斯州的那个危地马拉男孩的事
About the Guatemalan child in Texas...
国家安全顾问亚伦·肖尔
National Security Advisor Aaron Shore
为了与他的家人见面正在赶去厄尔巴索的路上
is on his way to El Paso now to meet with the family.
莫斯总统对这个问题非常直言不讳
President Moss has been very vocal about the issue.
总统是否打算回应
Does the president plan to respond?
首先  这不是一个问题  这关乎孩子的生命
First, it's not an issue, it's a child's life.
与前总统莫斯不同
And unlike former president Moss,
柯克曼总统并没有处理该煽动行为
President Kirkman doesn't deal in demagoguery.
但这种情况引发了公众对我国移民政策的真正质疑
But the situation raises real questions about immigration policy in this country.
总统会在适当的时候解决这些问题
They're questions the president is happy to address at the appropriate time.
所以你认为无证儿童应该接受医疗护理吗
So you think the undocumented child should receive medical care?
- 不  我没有这么说  - 这么说他不应该得到照顾了
- No, I didn't say that. - Then he shouldn't receive care.
我也没有这么说  这个问题  现在的情况显然非常复杂
I didn't say that, either. The issue... situation is obviously very complicated.
沉默是总统简化它的方式吗
Is silence the president's way of simplifying it?
下一个问题
Next question.
我不明白  这些名字是谁
I don't get it. Where are the names?
揭露他们的身份会使其他人处于危险之中
Revealing their identities puts others in danger.
为纪念美国中央情报局的成员
"In honor of those members of the Central Intelligence Agency
他们为报效国家献出了生命
who gave their lives in the service of their country."
如果克劳福德拉动扳机的速度快了一百纳秒  你就会在那里
If Crawford had been a nanosecond quicker pulling the trigger, you'd be up there.
我猜  还有更糟糕的死法
There are worse ways to go, I guess.
比如那些疯子造出的病毒吗
Like from a virus created by demented minds?
- 我们下一步做什么  - 观望
- What's our next step? - To the side.
这是国内的恐怖主义  联邦调查局正在接管
It's domestic terrorism. The FBI is taking over.
这完全是废话  这是一个全球的威胁
That's bloody bullshit. This is a global threat.
等等  你是说为了制造突变病毒  他们需要DNA片段吗
Wait, to make their mutant viruses, you said that they needed DNA pieces
这样他们才能把基因编辑到他们的生物武器中  对吗
that they could CRISPR into their bioweapon, right?
那么克劳福德他们从哪里获得这些DNA片段呢
So where did Crawford and his co-conspirators get those pieces?
我可以找人谈谈
There are people I could talk to.
这是一个自由的国家
Well, it is a free country.
我当然无法阻止你
I certainly couldn't stop you.
危地马拉的医疗保健系统陷入了严重的危机
The Guatemalan health-care system is in a deep crisis.
该国是的慢性营养不良比例排世界第四
The country has the fourth highest rate of chronic malnutrition in the world,
还有很高的孕产妇和儿童死亡率
high maternal and child mortality,
并且糖尿病和心脏病的患病率很高
and a large prevalence of diabetes and heart diseases.
许多家庭正处于
Many families living in...
总统先生  您没有必要这样做
Mr. President, you didn't have to.
如果我们只做我们必须做的事情  世界将多令人沮丧啊
What a dispiriting world it would be if we only did things we had to.
- 林恩还在昏迷中吗  - 是的
- Lynn's still unconscious. - Yeah.
医生认为这是偶然的
They believe it was accidental.
已经脱瘾治疗了  但他以前习以为常的大量的毒品
Having detoxed, the amount she was previously accustomed to using
可能导致她吸毒过量
could have caused her to OD.
马尔斯  我很抱歉
Mars, I'm so sorry.
你过得还好吧
How are you holding up?
- 我很好  谢谢你的关心  - 没关系
- I'm okay. Thanks for asking. - Of course.
你看到我们正在处理什么事了吧
You've seen what we've been dealing with?
- 生病的危地马拉小孩  - 他很不幸
- The sick Guatemalan kid. - It's tragic.
莫斯的人在到处宣扬这件事
Moss' guys are all over, making hay.
试图通过它点燃公众的反移民情绪
Using it to ignite anti-immigration sentiment.
我不敢相信他居然聘请了那个另类右翼的婊子养的做为他的首席战略家
I can't believe he hired that alt-right son of a bitch to be his chief strategist.
我也想干预  但以什么职权呢
I'd like to intervene, but under what authority?
让我来跟进这件事吧
Let me look into it.
- 你确定吗  - 能分分神也是好事
- Are you sure? - Grateful for the distraction.
谢谢你  我很感激
Thank you, I appreciate it.
先生  对不起打扰了
Sorry to interrupt, sir.
我刚刚收到你的竞选团队一员  但丁·埃文斯的消息
I just received word one of your campaign aides, Dontae Evans,
- 今天早上有人和他袭击  - 袭击吗
- was accosted this morning. - "Accosted"?
袭击者抢走了他的办公用手机
The attacker made off with his work phone,
但特勤组远程清空了手机里的所有内容
but the agency reassures the contents have been remotely wiped clean.
我不关心他手机里的内容  他本人怎么样了
I don't care about the contents of his phone. How is he?
面部挫伤  其实他正在这所医院接受治疗
Facial contusion he's receiving treatment for. Here, in fact.
- 请找到他的具体位置  - 是  先生
- Find out where exactly, please. - Yes, sir.
谢谢  居然在上班的路上被打劫
Thank you. Mugged, on his way to work?
很不幸  这种事并不稀罕
Sadly, it's not uncommon.
白宫助手在上岗培训时会被告知他们每5个人中就有1个早晚会遇到这种事
White House aides are told in orientation one in five can expect it at some point.
五分之一  太荒唐了
One in five? That's ridiculous.
为什么我第一次听说这种事
Why am I hearing about this for the first time?
您身在高位  接触不到这些事儿
It's a rung or 200 below your pay grade.
我要去看看他
I'm gonna go check on him.
谢谢你调查有关器官移植的事情
Thank you for looking into this transplant business.
- 别灰心  - 谢谢您
- Keep your chin up. - Thank you, sir.
民调显示中间选民在那孩子的事情上支持莫斯
Polls show the middle electorate sides with Moss on the kid.
想想吧  比起非法移民的孩子他们更喜欢钱包
They'd rather cozy up to pocketbooks than undocumented children, go figure.
别提你们的劳苦  贫困和疾病
Yeah, don't give us your tired, poor and sick.
除非你是个白人  对吧
Unless you're white, right?
媒体对这孩子真是穷追不舍  才早上十点我已经疲惫不堪了
The press is really hounding this kid. I'm exhausted and it's only 10:00 a.m.
可不是嘛  你点的什么
Tell me about it. What did you order?
四杯手冲美式咖啡
A quadruple-shot Americano pour-over.
能让我提起精神
Shh. It invigorates me.
你去参加媒体发布会的时候我会在贝塞斯达
Well, while you're briefing the hounds, I'll be in Bethesda.
我找到了一个我妈妈可以参加的临床试验
I think I found a clinical trial my mom qualifies for.
那太好了  你告诉你妈了吗
Hey, that's great. Have you told her yet?
没确定之前我不想让她抱太大希望
I don't want to get her hopes up until I'm sure, but I have to go.
- 享受你的能量饮料吧  - 谢谢
- Enjoy that energy drink. - Yeah, thanks.
埃尔皮索 德克萨斯
政治家先生
Hey, Mr. Politician!
我女儿因为没得到及时的骨髓移植而死掉了
My daughter died 'cause she didn't get a bone marrow transplant in time!
你和你那名不正言不顺的总统
Now you and your illegitimate president
却想让我们的孩子在移植名单上越排越靠后
want to shove our kids further down the waiting list
让一个非法入境的寄生虫插队
so some undocumented parasite can jump the line!
你好
Hello.
- 下午好  - 下午好
- Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
- 幸会  - 幸会
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
马特奥
Mateo.
- 我叫亚伦  - 您好先生
- My name is Aaron. - Hello, sir.
我给你带了点儿东西来
I brought you something.
是总统办公室送给你的
It's from the office of the president.
- 是什么  - 打开来看看吧
- What is it? - Open it and see.
能请您帮我戴上吗
Can you put it on me, please?
当然
Yes.
让我们来看看
Let's see...
戴在哪只小狗上比较好呢
Which puppy are we going to put it on?
戴在这儿吧
We're going to put it up here.
马特奥  看上去很配你啊
It looks good on you, Mateo.
很棒
Very good.
- 他是个可爱的孩子  - 谢谢
- He's a lovely boy. - Thank you.
谢谢您能来
And thank you for coming.
谢谢您  可是如果他得不到器官移植
Yes, thank you, but if he doesn't receive a transplant
而我们被驱逐出境
and we're deported...
恐怕我的儿子会死掉
I'm afraid my son will die.
医院说如果没有透析治疗他活不了几天
They told us he wouldn't live more than a few days without dialysis.
我明白
I understand.
医生说鲁本与马特奥配型成功了
The doctor told us that Ruben is a match for Mateo.
- 配型成功了吗  - 是的
-He's a match? - Yes.
请稍等
One moment, please.
肖先生  我是肾脏移植外科主任
Mr. Shore, I'm Julie Snow,
茱莉·斯诺
Surgical Director of Kidney Transplantation.
幸会
It's a pleasure.
这位是我们的首席顾问  尼尔·克里斯托夫
This is our chief counsel, Neal Kristof.
好的  现在是什么情况
Right. So, where are we with all this?
马特奥自从到来我们一直在做透析
We've been dialyzing Mateo since he arrived.
我们遵循的是联邦法案  因为这是急诊
Guided by federal law because it's an emergency.
但是一旦他的疗程结束  我们就得让他出院
However, once he's finished this course, we're gonna have to discharge him.
出院  他需要移植手术啊
Discharge him? I mean, he needs a transplant.
非法移民是不能进入UNOS移植名单的
Undocumented immigrants can't be placed on the UNOS transplantation list.
我明白
I'm aware of that.
但是孩子的妈妈说孩子的父亲配型成功了  是吗
But his mom just told me that his father was a match. Is that right?
是的  不过
It is, but...
不过什么
But?
手术要27万美元
The surgery costs $270,000.
很遗憾  除非有人愿意掏这笔钱
Unfortunately, unless someone were to step in and foot the bill,
否则我们无法给他做手术
we can't perform the procedure.
- 那么说现在是钱的问题喽  - 对于医院来说  是的
-So, this is about money now? - For the hospital, yes.
我们尽量不参与政治  那是您的职责  不是我们的
We try to stay out of the politics. That's your job, not ours.
好
Okay.
我们获悉小马特奥如果不接受肾脏移植
Little Mateo, we are told, will die
而被遣返危地马拉  他将必死无疑
if he is sent back to Guatemala without a kidney transplant.
危地马拉
Guatemala is one
是拉丁美洲最贫穷的国家之一
of the poorest countries in Latin America
我是马尔斯·哈珀
Mars Harper.
马尔斯  我拿到你想要的了
Hey, Mars. I got what you asked for.
卫生和公共服务法规他妈的像个老鼠窝
Health and Human Service regs are a fucking rat's nest.
只有你才能找得到奶酪
If anybody can find the cheese, it's you.
说的没错  听听这条
Damn right. All right, get this.
卫生与公共服务部长
"The secretary of HHS has the authority
有权为特需人群中增加器官移植数量
to increase transplantation among populations with special needs,
特需人群包括少数民族群体的后代
including children who are members of racial or ethnic minority groups."
这怎么能帮我们筹到马特奥手术需要的钱呢
How does that help us get the cash for Mateo's transplant?
公共卫生服务部有一个700万美元的资金池
There's a $7-million pot
可以自由分配使用
the Public Health Service can distribute at its discretion.
这个你肯定乐意听
And you'll love this.
法规并未明令禁止救治非法移民
The regs don't specifically prohibit treating undocumented immigrants.
如果他们不遵守这个法规我们可以告他们
So we can sue their asses if they don't comply with the regs.
你猜是谁忘了堵上这个漏洞
And guess who forgot to close this little loophole?
科尔尼·莫斯  这些法规是在他在位时编写的
Corny Moss. These regs were written under his administration.
太好了  莫斯要为马特奥的手术买单
I love it. Moss is gonna be the one to pay for Mateo's surgery.
把这个好消息告诉总统
Give POTUS the good news.
准备出发  人出来了
All right, we're moving. And out.
出发
Come on. Let's go.
这待阅超规格了  先生
This is over and above, sir.
这是最起码我该做的  送你去哪儿
The least I could do. Where are we headed?
竞选办公室
The campaign office.
那可不行  你今天不要工作了  你住哪儿
Not a chance. You're not working today. Where do you live?
布伦特伍德  我在那儿长大的
Brentwood, where I grew up.
那一带我不熟
I'm not familiar with that neighborhood.
- 不奇怪  - 为什么这么说
- Hmm, I'm not surprised. - Why do you say that?
因为大多数白人从没去过那儿
Because most white folks have never been there,
尽管那里离国会大厦只有10分钟车程
even though it's ten minutes from the Capitol.
我想看看你生活的地方  请你带我转转
I'd like to see where you live. I'd like you to show me.
先生们  咱们去布伦特伍德
Gentlemen, we're going to Brentwood.
- 总统先生  - 我们送但丁回家  谢谢
- Sir? - We're gonna take Dontae home. Thank you.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
我的小学
My elementary school.
还有铁丝网  看上去像个监狱
Razor wire. It looks like a prison.
进门时还有金属探测仪  我放学回家都不敢直接走回去
Metal detectors when you walk in. I couldn't walk straight home to my house.
在帮派的地盘上得左躲右闪地挑路走
I had to zigzag around, pick your way through the gang turf.
从我记事起杂货商店就关门了
Grocery store's been closed since I can remember.
- 那你们家在哪儿买东西  - 不在这附近
-Where does your family shop? - Nowhere around here.
我们管这叫食物荒漠
We call those "food deserts."
我当总统之前曾提交一个计划试图解决这个问题
Before I became president, I proposed a plan to try and combat them.
不幸的是里士满政府另有重要的安排
Unfortunately, the Richmond administration had other priorities.
计划未必成现实
Plans don't often become reality.
我从未见过这些  这让我很羞愧
I'm embarrassed that I've never seen this before.
这里离白宫几分钟的路程
It's just a few miles from the White House.
谢谢您  先生
Thank you, sir.
不  但丁  我要谢谢你让我看到这些
No, Dontae, thank you for showing me.
你确定你没事了吗
Are you sure you're gonna be all right?
是的先生
Yes, sir.
那好  明天见
Okay, see you tomorrow.
她刚刚经历了一场化疗的考验
She's already been through a gauntlet of chemo.
真因为如此免疫疗法对她来说是最佳选择
Which is why immunotherapy might be her best bet.
我们的实验疗法增强了免疫系统的反应
Our experimental treatment amplifies the immune system's response.
我们靶向一个在上皮卵巢癌中
We target a folate receptor,
过度表达的叶酸受体
which is over-expressed in epithelial ovarian cancer.
她将每隔几周接受一次静脉注射
She'd receive an IV dosage once every few weeks.
迄今有效果吗
Has there been any luck so far?
对于效果我们很兴奋  但还缺乏纵向历史数据
We're heartened, but we're lacking longitudinal data.
为什么
How come?
绝大多数患者都是癌症晚期  数据积累比较困难
It's difficult when most participants are at an advanced stage.
她可以  她处于恢复期已经两年了
Well, she beat it. She was in remission for two years.
我看过她的所有资料后会打电话给你
I'll call you when I've reviewed all her records.
非常感谢  这是让人难以置信的好消息
Thank you so much. This is so incredible to hear.
那我们的确有合法权力去迫使医院介入
So, we do have the legal authority to force the hospital's hand.
根据M和N小节条款是这样的
According to subsections M and N.
孩子父亲是合适供体  那些关于移植美国人的肾脏的抗议也没用了
The father being a match removes the "taking an American kidney" objection.
我们还在等民调的结果
We're still waiting to see how this polls.
我不想等了  执行吧
I'm not. Give the go-ahead.
反对挽救一个孩子的性命的人
Anyone who objects to saving a child's life,
我乐意奉陪到底  干得不错
I'll be more than happy to engage with. Nice work.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
- 我把这个好消息告诉艾伦  - 我来告诉他
-I'll give Aaron the good news. - I'll tell him.
好  当然
Right. Sure, of course.
既然已经这样了  我们不妨做到实至名归
Uh, so, since this is happening, we may as well own it.
让艾伦和那个男孩一起上电视
Let's get Aaron on TV with the boy.
- 靠得近点儿  - 要带个人情感色彩
-Lean in. - Personalize it.
一次死亡是一场悲剧  一百万次死亡只是个统计数字
One death is a tragedy, a million deaths, a statistic.
你心中的英雄斯大林的话
Stalin, your hero.
买下这本杂志  不然我们就杀了这狗狗
Buy this magazine or we'll kill the dog.
嗯  差不多吧  去干活吧
Yeah, something like that. Go, get to work.
好
Okay.
先生  你找我吗
Sir, you needed me?
我能问你一个个人问题吗
Can I ask you a personal question?
当然
Of course.
你来上班的路上遇到过打劫吗
Have you ever been mugged on your way to work here?
迄今为止还没有  我比较幸运
Uh, not so far, sir. I've been lucky.
幸运
Lucky.
科尔曼·哈里斯是乔治城大学
Coleman Harris is a professor
城市规划方面的教授
of Urban Planning at Georgetown University.
能请他尽快到我这儿来吗
Let's see if we can get him here as quickly as possible.
- 是  先生  - 谢谢
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
真幸运
"Lucky."
下午好  感谢大家的到来
Good afternoon, and thank you everyone for coming.
回到德州的家中总是让人开心
It's always nice to come back home to Texas.
今天来到这里让我想起了
Being here today reminds me of the first time
我四年级时第一次住进医院的情景
I ever landed in a hospital when I was in fourth grade.
我有阑尾炎  幸运的是  我们获得了医疗保健
I had appendicitis. Luckily, we had access to health care.
他们治好我  几天后我就回家了
They fixed me up. I was back home in a couple days.
这是马特奥·奥雷利亚纳
Now, this is Mateo Orellana.
上个星期你们听到了很多关于他的事
You've heard a lot about him this last week,
但是我认为你们最好去了解他
but I thought it best for you to get to know him.
现在  马特奥喜欢足球  热巧克力和复仇者联盟  马特奥
Now, Mateo likes soccer, hot chocolate and the Avengers. Mateo?
你最喜欢的复仇者是谁
Who is your favorite Avenger?
浩克
Hulk!
马特奥和我生病时差不多大
Mateo is about the same age I was when I got sick.
但他来自危地马拉
But he's from Guatemala,
那里没有针对他的医疗方案
where medical options for his condition are nonexistent.
所以他的父母做了任何慈爱的父母都会做的事
So his parents did what any loving parent would do.
他们把马特奥带到一个
They brought Mateo to the one place
他们所知他生存机会最大的地方  美国
they knew he had the best chance of surviving, the United States.
我们可以拯救马特奥
We can save Mateo
而无需将任何人从器官资源共享网络移植名单中移除
without displacing anyone from the UNOS transplantation list.
马特奥的父亲已经准备好并愿意献出自己的肾脏来挽救儿子的生命
Mateo's father is ready and willing to give his kidney to save his son's life.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
只要我们有选择的余地  我们就有特权
Any time we have options, we're in a position of privilege.
它需要的是密切关注和悉心照顾
It requires close attention and great care
而不是互相伤害  是伸出援助之手
not to hurt one another, but to reach out a hand and help.
我想我们欠彼此太多  我会回答一些问题
I think we owe one another that much. I'll take some questions.
你老婆真是太幸运了
Your wife was pretty damn lucky.
有人这么告诉过我
So I've been told.
我不知道见过多少人在服了阿片类药物后匆匆赶来
Can't tell you how many folks I've seen rushed in here after OD-ing on opiates.
他们停止呼吸  有人发现他们然后报警
They stop breathing, someone finds 'em, calls 911, they get put on a vent.
这是终生的脑损伤
It's brain damage for life.
- 林恩会没事的  - 这次
- Lynn is gonna be okay. - Well, this time.
你最好随身带些纳洛酮  以防万一
You better keep some Narcan on hand, just in case.
在重症监护室要花多少钱
How much does this ICU cost?
用你的自付额  大概和在乔治敦的
With your co-pay, probably about the same
高档餐厅吃几顿饭差不多
as a couple of dinners at a fancy Georgetown restaurant.
但是对于没有保险的人呢
But for someone without insurance?
嗯  这张门票至少要花6万美元
Well, this admission would run you about 60,000 bucks at least.
就像你说的  非常幸运
Like you said, pretty damn lucky.
科尔曼  很高兴见到你  感谢您的光临
Coleman. So good to see you. Thank you for coming.
谢谢你的邀请
Thanks for the invite.
请坐  有多久了
Please. How long has it been?
自从哥伦比亚吗  五年  或在位高权重之前
Since Columbia? Five years. Or two influential positions ago for you.
我早就该请你过来一趟了  我很抱歉
I should've had you in here a long time ago. I'm sorry.
是我的错
Guilty as charged.
- 现在你在竞选连任  - 是的  但这不是我让你来的原因
- And now you're running for reelection. - Yes, but that's not why I asked you here.
我刚刚了解到  五分之一的白宫工作人员
I've just learned that one in five White House staffers
在上班途中可能会遭遇抢劫
can expect to be mugged on their way to work.
我认为这是可耻的
And I think that's disgraceful.
因为这发生在特权阶层精英身上
Because it's happening to privileged, elite people?
不  因为这是美国的首都
No, because this is the capital of the United States,
我们应该成为一个榜样  我们可以做得更好
and we should be an example. We can do better.
我参观了一下  然后读了您关于
I took a little tour, then read your report
关于低收入社区不利健康状况
on environmental contributors to adverse health conditions
- 的环境因素的报告  - 你了解了
- in lower-income communities. - You keep up.
这很有意思
It's fascinating stuff.
我知道蟑螂成灾与哮喘有关
I learned that cockroach infestation is related to asthma.
慢性耳部感染导致阅读能力下降
Chronic ear infections to poor reading skills.
缺乏新鲜水果和蔬菜导致肥胖
A lack of access to fresh fruits and vegetables
2型糖尿病  以及随之而来的一切
to obesity, type 2 diabetes, and everything else that could follow.
所有这些都很容易预防  比如亚特兰大计划
All easily preventable. Like the Atlanta project.
是的  是为特定目的而建的社区
The purpose-built community, yes.
这个想法  改变了社区环境本身
The idea, transform the community environment itself.
清理  修理  改进或恢复服务
Cleanup, repairs, improve or restore services.
解决居民间的邻里关系
Fix the neighborhood out from under the residents.
住宅高档化无位移  我想在这试试
Gentrification without displacement. I want to try that here.
这需要资金
It costs money.
你在亚特兰大是怎么做到的
How'd you accomplish it in Atlanta?
一个捐助者  以及一些地方和国家基金
A benefactor, along with some local and state funds.
我希望你能参与其中
I want you to be a part of this.
迟做比不做好
Better late than never.
没错
Yeah.
白宫的艺术收藏品包括6.5万件物品和500幅画作
The White House art collection includes 65,000 objects and 500 paintings.
它们不可能都在这里展出
They can't be all on display here.
哦  不  当我的姐夫成为总统时
Oh, no. When my brother-in-law became president,
他和我已故的姐姐从收藏品中挑选了一些作品
he and my late sister selected works from the collection,
还有从国家美术馆借来的画  比如这幅
as well as paintings on loan from the National Gallery, like this one.
约翰·辛格尔顿·科普利的《华生与鲨鱼》
Watson and the Shark by John Singleton Copley.
非常震撼
It's quite striking.
它描述了在哈瓦那港营救一个
It depicts the rescue of an orphan boy
被鲨鱼袭击的孤儿
attacked by a shark in Havana Harbor.
对总统来说  这是一个奇怪的选择吗
An odd choice, no, for a president?
相反  总统非常喜欢描绘战胜
On the contrary. The president is quite drawn to paintings
逆境和坚韧之美的画作
that depict triumph over adversity and the beauty of resilience.
说得好  柯克曼总统在这次选举中肯定要面对鲨鱼
Well said. President Kirkman certainly is facing sharks during this election.
就像那个可怕的莫斯
Like that awful Moss,
斥责那个需要移植的可怜小男孩
berating that poor little boy who needs a transplant.
你们国家怎么能这样对待一个孩子呢
How can your country treat a child this way?
有时  我的国家会有一颗冷漠的心
At times, my country can have a cold heart.
我搬到法国的原因之一
One of the reasons I moved to France
是因为你相信医疗保健是一项人权
was because you believe health care is a human right.
我们还相信
We also believe that children
儿童有受教育  住房和言论自由的权利
have the right to an education, housing, and to free expression.
贵国是唯一没有批准保护所有
Your country is the only one not to ratify the UN Convention
儿童权利的联合国公约的国家
that protects the right of all children.
为什么总统没有签名
Why hasn't the president signed it?
他是支持的  但参议院必须批准它
He supports it. The Senate must ratify it.
那么他应该向参议院施加压力
Then he should put pressure on the Senate.
也许我们应该继续前进
Perhaps we should move on.
你们的艺术品很惊艳
Your art is impressive,
但你们对孩子们的态度还有许多不足之处
but your treatment of children leaves much to be desired.
- 麦克米兰副理事  - 威尔斯女士
- Deputy Director McMillan. - Ms. Wells.
我看到你增加了你的死亡人数
I see you've upped your body count.
事实上  只有一个
Just the one, actually.
要是有机会采访克劳福德就好了
It would've been nice to have had a chance to interview Crawford.
在我压制他之前  我确实回答了几个问题
I did get a few questions off before I had to neutralize him.
他不太愿意说
He was less than forthcoming.
他的硬盘里有更多的成果
His hard drive bore a little more fruit,
但是  我的意思是  这家伙确实是一个火箭科学家
but, I mean, the guy was literally a rocket scientist,
聪明到不会留下大的文件痕迹
so smart enough not to leave a huge paper trail.
他留下痕迹了吗
And the trail he did leave?
带领我们加入了  复兴我们的国家  组织
Led us to the group Reclaim Our Nation.
联邦调查局已经知道了
Which the FBI already knew about.
它也证实了一些你没有证实的事情
Well, it also confirmed something that you didn't.
克劳福德是导致在多伦多的失策和
That Crawford was behind the genetically modified flus
坦帕市针对有色人种的转基因流感的幕后推手
that were causing miscarriages in Toronto and targeting people of color in Tampa.
还有其他的吗
Anything else?
是的  他最后说了几句
Yeah, he had some final words.
他说  这件事比我重要得多  你不可能阻止它
He said, "This is so much bigger than me, and you're not going to stop it."
表示威胁迫在眉睫
Indicating an imminent threat.
是的  还有可能存在一个同谋
Yes, and the possible existence of a co-conspirator
他就在那  已经准备好实施计划了
who's out there, ready and willing to execute.
显然是他的仇恨集团
His hate group, obviously.
我们没有找到任何证据来证实这一点
We didn't find any evidence to corroborate that.
我们跟踪调查了在怀俄明的一块飞地
We've tracked Reclaim Our Nation to an enclave in Wyoming.
我们明天突袭它  你现在可以把文件交接给我了
We raid it tomorrow. I'll take your files now.
我想一起去那儿
I'd like to be there.
等我们办完这件事
When we're finished here,
联邦调查局就不需要汉娜·威尔斯的进一步协助了
the FBI will require no further assistance from Hannah Wells.
你是想拿这张账单骗我吗  格雷戈里
Are you shitting me with this bill, Gregory?
你应该阻止艾伦把我榨干
You're supposed to keep Alan from bleeding me dry.
我要付给我律师的钱比我前夫的还多
I'm gonna end up paying my lawyer more than my ex-husband.
不  我不能再坐在另一个调解室里
Well, no, I can't sit through another mediation
看着他那谄媚  贪财的嘴脸了
looking at his smarmy, gold-digging face.
给我砍个最低价  我真的是受够了
Cut me the best deal you can. I'm just done.
天啊
God.
帮我个忙  快他妈给我个好消息
Do me a favor, give me some fucking good news.
好吧  最新的民意调查数据显示了对马特奥的大量支持
OK,Well, the latest polling data indicates a groundswell of support for Mateo.
他在我们所关心的美国过得怎么样
How's he doing in the states we care about?
铁锈地带的重磅炸弹  而且在德克萨斯州还在增长
Gangbusters in the Rust Belt, and it's growing in Texas.
天哪  这孩子真是天赐之物  他什么时候动手术
Holy cow, the kid is a godsend. When is his surgery?
明天早上  人们很感兴趣
Tomorrow morning, and people are invested.
觉得亚伦应该再开一次记者会
I think Aaron should do another press conference.
我希望能穿上紧身装
In really tight scrubs, I'm hoping.
好吧  你今晚就呆在这  你知道的  监控之类的事情
Okay, you stay here tonight, and, you know, monitor things.
我妈妈要从佛罗里达飞过来和我住在一起  所以
My mother is flying in from Florida to stay with me, so...
我不是怪物  你为什么不去给她把门打开
Well, I'm not a monster. Why don't you go and let her in,
给她一个大大的拥抱  然后回到这工作
give her a big hug, and then get your ass back here?
好吧
Okay.
这些都很旧了
Those are stale.
助餐厅收集了所有他们没有卖出去的糖果
The cafeteria gathers up all the candy bars they haven't sold
把它们塞到这里给我们这样的夜猫子吃
and sticks them in here for night owls like us,
他们在凌晨4点什么都吃
who'll eat anything at 4:00 a.m.
我几乎尝不出它的味道
I can barely taste it.
你说谁病了
Who've you got sick?
我的妻子
My wife.
想聊聊吗
Want to talk about it?
- 不太想  - 我理解
- Not really. - I understand.
我希望我能理解
I wish I understood.
我认为人类天生就想要答案
I think human beings are wired to want answers,
而原因却不容易解释
reasons for what isn't easily explained.
我妻子吸毒成瘾
My wife's addicted to opiates.
她想要好转吗
Does she want to get better?
- 我不知道  - 你想怎么样
- I don't know. - What do you want?
我也不知道
I don't know, either.
- 这是一个困境  - 你的专长  是吧
- That's a quandary. - Your specialty, huh?
我的使命  你今晚有什么想法吗
My calling. So what's on your mind tonight?
我不知道该怎么
I don't know what to do.
如果我离开她  我会感到内疚
If I leave her, I'll feel guilty.
如果我留下  不知道什么时候接到电话
If I stay, I'll be miserable not knowing
一切都结束了  我会很痛苦
when I'm gonna get that call that it's all over.
她必须朝好的方向看  那不是你的责任
She has to want to get better. That's not on you.
但也不全是她的错
But it's not all on her, either.
你在其中扮演什么角色
What's your role in this?
我出柜
My cheating.
都是因为我
That's on me.
我工作到很晚  所以我不必回家
My working late so I don't have to come home.
那也是因为我
That's on me, too.
那就改变你的行为  你能做的就这么多
Then change your behavior. That much you can do.
人们认为这很复杂
Folks think it's so complicated.
他们都被自己的人际关系和生活所纠缠
They're all tangled up in their relationships and lives.
但他们往往没有意识到他们有选择
But they often don't realize that they have choices.
他们可以留下  也可以离开  他们可以诚实  也可以撒谎
They can stay or they can go. They can be honest or lie.
也许是时候让你做出一些艰难的决定
Maybe it's time for you to make some hard decisions
停止为过去责备自己和妻子了
and stop blaming yourself and your wife for the past.
棒棒糖其实很好吃
Candy bar is actually pretty good.
我们的大好时机
Our timing couldn't be better.
我们的情报显示因克劳福德之死召开了紧急峰会
Our intel says an emergency summit was called over Crawford's death.
我们每个人都在其中
We have every damn one of them in there.
你应该给威尔斯警官寄张感谢卡
You should send Officer Wells a thank-you card.
我建议你留意一下那个
I would suggest you keep eyes on that one.
当她没有被邀请参加行动的时候  她就变得十分暴力
When she doesn't get invited to the party, she gets volatile.
周边很安全
The perimeter is secure.
表演时间
Show time.
所有队伍都已就位  准备就绪
All teams are in place and good to go.
我数到三  3  2  1
On my count. Three, two, one...
破门
Breach.
什么鬼东西
What the hell is this?
他们全都死了
They're dead. Every last one of them.
把防弹衣拿过来
Get HAZMAT in here!
他们的血到处都是  所有人撤退
They've all bled out. Everybody fall back.
妈妈  你好吗
Mom. How are you?
- 我从没让你放心过  - 她需要躺下
- I never did fly well. - She needs to lie down.
这就是我一直称赞的蒂娜
This is Tina that I've been raving about.
她会照顾我的  这样我就不会那么麻烦了
She'll be taking care of me so that I'm not such of a bother.
很高兴见到你  蒂娜  妈妈  你从来都不是个麻烦
Nice to meet you, Tina. And, Mom, you're never a bother.
哦  我有个好消息  我见过国家卫生研究所的人
Oh, I have some great news. I met with someone at the NIH,
你已经被接受了试验性治疗
and you've been accepted into a trial therapy.
这是最有希望的治疗方法
It's the most promising thing out there for a cure.
我太累了  现在不想这件事
I'm too tired to think about that right now.
你下班回家后我们谈谈
Let's talk when you get home from work.
我今天不去上班了
I'm not gonna go to work today.
去吧
Go.
如果你和柯克曼总统谈过  告诉他别担心
And if you talk to President Kirkman, tell him not to worry.
我们离开前我通过邮件投了票
I voted by mail before we left.
高夫部长  请坐
Secretary Goff. Please, have a seat.
哦  当你竞选的时候
Oh, when you're campaigning,
几乎不可能完成任何其他事情
it seems next to impossible to get anything else done.
但我想让你们知道  如果我们有幸获
But I wanted to let you know that if we're fortunate enough to win,
我希望你继续领导
I would like you to continue leading
住房和城市发展部
the Department of Housing and Urban Development.
我很荣幸能接手你们在那里开展的工作
I would be honored to continue the work you started there.
不幸的是  我在那里的时间不够长  无法完成我希望完成的任务
Unfortunately, I wasn't there long enough to accomplish what I'd hoped to.
而作为总统  似乎永远都没有足够的时间
And as president, there never seems to be enough time to go around.
- 你的财政年度结束日就要到了  对吗  - 是的
- Your fiscal year-end is coming up, right? - It is.
你疯狂地寻找把剩下的资金花出去的方法
You're in that frantic search of where to spend the rest of your funding
这样你的预算就不会被下一笔拨款切断
so your budget doesn't get cut off by the next appropriations.
你知道规矩
You know the drill.
今天可能是你的幸运日
Well, today might be your lucky day,
因为我知道你想把钱花在哪
because I think I have an idea where you might want to spend that money.
医生  马特奥成功的机会有多大
Doctor, what are Mateo's chances here?
机会很大
They're very good.
活体供体移植的短期和长期存活率
Living donor transplants have better short and long-term survival rates
都高于死亡供体移植
than deceased donor recipients.
我们更需要担心的是他的病后护理和治疗
It's his after-care we need to be more worried about.
好吧  跟我说说
Okay, talk to me about that.
手术后他需要服用免疫抑制剂  这样他的身体才不会
He'll need immunosuppressant medication after the procedure
排斥新的肾脏  这并不便宜
so that his body doesn't reject the new kidney. It's not cheap.
需要花费多少
What's the cost?
如果你没有保险  花费金额可能高达17000美元一年
If you're uninsured, it can run upward of 17,000 a year.
需要多少年
And how many years will he need it?
每年都是  他的整个余生
Every year, for the rest of his life.
我得去手术室了
I've gotta get to the OR.
嘿  小伊
Hey, Isi.
嘿  亲爱的  他做完手术了吗
Hey, love. Is he out of surgery yet?
大约一个半小时左右
About an hour and a half or so.
我在踱步  好像他是我自己的孩子似的
I'm pacing like he's my own kid or something.
哦  小男子汉让你担心了  是吧
Aw. Little muchacho got to you, huh?
听着  我想问你件事
Hey, listen, I wanted to ask you something.
《美国卫生与公众服务部法典》是否有涵盖
Are there any provisions in the HHS code
移植病人术后护理的规定
that cover after-care for transplant patients?
不  它只涉及采购和分配
No, it only addressed procurement and allocation.
这里的医生告诉我  马特奥的抗排异药物
The doctor here is telling me that Mateo's anti-rejection drugs
将使他每年花费1.7万美元
will run him about 17 grand a year.
现在  如果马特奥活到70岁  那就超过100万了
Now, if Mateo lives 70 years, that's a bit over a million.
这太吓人了
That's freaking outrageous.
不过  要正确看待这个问题  也没有那么多
Put it in perspective, though. It's not that much.
等等  120万不是很多吗
Wait, 1.2 million is not that much?
当你把它和竞选活动的花费进行比较时  你就会发现事实并非如此
Not when you compare it to what gets spent on election campaigns.
20亿美元  这才是他妈的无耻
$2 billion this cycle? That's fucking outrageous.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
我说了什么不对的话吗
What did I say?
不  你只是给了我一个主意  我马上给你回电话
No, you just gave me an idea. I'll call you right back.
我想今天晚些时候我们可以把你妻子的管子拔掉了
I think we can extubate your wife later today.
- 她几乎可以自己呼吸了  - 那就放心了
- She's almost ready to breathe on her own. - That's a relief.
现在  治疗的下一步是让她停止服用阿片类药物
Now, the next step in her treatment is to wean her off the opioids.
她去了三次戒毒所这是行不通的
Well, she's gone to rehab three times. So, that's not working.
好消息是  我们有一种新药正在三期试验中
Well, the good news is we have a new drug that's in phase three trials.
它已被成功地用于减少依赖性
It's been successfully used to decrease dependency
和减少过量用药的危险
and reduce the dangers of overdosing.
这就解释了其中的风险和好处
This explains the risks, the benefits.
我建议你和哈珀夫人考虑一下
I'd recommend you and Mrs. Harper consider it.
- 还没上市吗  - 没有  但很快就会有的
- It's not on the market yet? - No, but it will be soon.
如果食品及药物管理局最终批准的话  会非常有希望
If the FDA gives final approval. Results have been very promising.
它是由乔丹·弗拉格旗下的弗拉格金德公司生产的
It's made by FlagKind, owned by Jordan Flagg.
- 嗯  你认识他吗  - 我们在俱乐部打网球
- Mmm-hmm. You know him? - We play tennis at our club.
他对疼痛管理很有经验
He has a lot of experience in pain management.
他妈的确实知道  是他制造了让她上瘾的鬼东西
The fuck he does. He made the shit that she's hooked on.
现在他又要向她收取治疗毒瘾的新药的费用吗
And now he wants to charge her for a new drug to treat her addiction?
不不不  不收费  它还在试验中
No, no, no, there's no charge. It's still in trials.
你想把我老婆当实验品
Oh, so you want to use my wife as a guinea pig
让这个吸血鬼更有钱吗
to make this bloodsucker even richer?
免了
We pass.
嗯  你妻子一两天内就能回家了
Well, your wife should be able to go home in a day or two.
- 祝你们俩好运  - 再见
- I wish you both good luck. - Goodbye.
谢谢大家的出席
Thank you all for attending.
我想借此机会告诉你们
I wanted to take this moment to inform you,
作为国会黑人核心小组的成员
as members of the Congressional Black Caucus,
住房和城市发展部试点项目将于今天晚些时候宣布
that a HUD pilot project will be announced later today.
这将彻底振兴位于华盛顿特区的
One that will completely revitalize
布伦特伍德低收入社区
the low-income neighborhood of Brentwood right here in Washington, DC.
作为一个模型  我们计划使用亚特兰大
As a model, we are planning to use
非常成功的专门建设的社区
the highly successful purpose-built community in Atlanta,
并希望它能为全国未来的项目树立榜样
and hope that it will serve as an example for future projects across the country.
帮助你赢得黑人的选票吗
And help you win black votes?
我理解你那冷嘲热讽的话
I understand the cynicism of your remark.
只要有候选人参选
As long as there have been candidates for office,
他们对黑人选民所关心的问题只是嘴上说说而已
they have paid lip service to the concerns of black voters.
但我不仅仅是一个候选人
But I am not just a candidate.
我是现任美国总统
I am the sitting president of the United States.
我并不是对未来的行动做出空洞的承诺
And I'm not making hollow promises for some future action.
不管我能否赢得选举  这个项目都会成功
This project is gonna happen whether I win the election or not.
我们期待着细节
We look forward to the details.
但出于尊重  你并没有让我们所有人
But with respect, you didn't ask us all here
在这里礼貌地提醒你
to deliver a courtesy heads-up.
不  如果你不介意的话  我想引用你在党团会议上的座右铭
No, if you'll indulge me, I would like to quote your caucus motto.
黑人没有永远的朋友  没有永远的敌人
"Black people have no permanent friends, no permanent enemies,
只有永远的利益
just permanent interests."
我认为莫斯政府不会为这些利益服务
I don't believe a Moss administration will serve those interests.
我们的选民在很大程度上认同民主党
Our constituents largely identify as Democrats.
恕我直言  波特在民调中排名第三  而且他的支持率正在下降
With all due respect, Porter's polling third and he's fading.
他要输了
He is going to lose.
如果我们支持你  我们怎么
How can we trust that you'll follow through
能相信你会坚持到底呢
if we give you our endorsement?
这种情况以前发生过无数次
This has happened countless times before.
当你领导住房和城市发展部时  你承诺解决食品荒漠问题
When you ran HUD, you promised to address food deserts.
那些承诺没有兑现
Those were promises unkept.
就像我之前说的  这个项目就要开始了
As I said earlier, this project is going to happen.
它可能会被抛弃  也可能是我们
It can either be an orphan
一生中第一个真正有意义的全国性
or the beginning of the first truly meaningful nationwide
城市重建计划的开始
urban renewal program of our lifetimes.
你看  我相信我们的利益是一致的
You see, I believe our interests are aligned.
马特奥的手术结束了
So, Mateo's out of surgery.
医生说事情进展得很顺利
The doctors say things went as well as they could have gone.
他和他的父亲都恢复得很好
Both he and his father are recovering nicely,
他们应该在接下来的几天内就可以出院
and they should be discharged in the next couple of days.
现在  我们遇到了另一个问题
Now, here's where we run into another issue.
你看  马特奥  和每个移植受者一样
You see, Mateo, like every transplant recipient,
他需要抗排斥药物
will need what's called anti-rejection medication
来保持肾脏健康
in order to keep his kidney healthy.
他的余生都需要这种药物
He will need this medication for the rest of his life.
事实上  像奥雷拉纳这样的人
The fact that people like the Orellanas,
以及许多工薪阶层的美国人
and many working-class Americans, can't afford this medication,
都买不起这种药  这种药太贵了
the fact that this medication is so expensive,
这是另一个话题
now that's a discussion for another time.
现在最紧迫的是我们要想办法给马特奥
What's most pressing now is that we find a way
提供他需要的药物  这是我的想法
to give Mateo the medication he needs. And here's my pitch.
现在是选举季  也许你想
It's election season,
给柯克曼的竞选活动捐点钱
and maybe you were thinking of kicking in a few bucks to the Kirkman campaign,
或者科尼利厄斯·莫斯或威廉·波特
or Cornelius Moss or William Porter.
现在  你为什么不把  马特奥  发短信到70773呢
Now, instead, why don't you text "Mateo" to 70773?
它将立即向马特奥的基金注入10美元
It'll instantly send $10 to Mateo's fund.
我将是第一个做这件事的人
I'll be the first one to do it.
让我们从政治中休息一下  专注于真正重要的事情
Let's take a break from politics and focus on what really matters.
发送  马特奥  到70773
"Mateo" to 70773.
感谢你们
Thank you.
- 没错  -  没错  乔丹
- Yeah. - That's right, Jordan.
这个项目将是更广泛计划的首例
This project will be the first of a broader program,
以改造这片伟大土地上每个角落被忽视的社区
transforming neglected neighborhoods in every corner of this great land.
柯克曼总统会见了国会黑人核心小组的领导人
President Kirkman met with the leaders of the Congressional Black Caucus,
他们倾力支持这个项目
and they threw their support behind the project...
我猜这事儿也有你一份功劳
I gather you played a role in this.
我在几年前和一个白人男子共事时
Guess I should've gotten mugged
遭到了行凶抢劫
working for an important white dude years ago.
这是件好事  不是吗
It's kind of a good thing, no?
也许吧  如果这不仅是嘴上说说以得到黑人选票
I guess. If it's not just paying lip service to get the black vote.
- 你觉得美国总统会做到吗  - 他不会是第一个
- You think POTUS would do that? - He wouldn't be the first.
嗨  妈妈
Hey, Mom.
我的天哪  你在看这个吗
Oh, my God, are you watching this?
是啊
Yeah.
我的宝贝和这个事有关吗
Did my baby have anything to do with it?
也许有一点儿
Maybe a little.
艾伦  艾伦  艾伦
Aaron! Aaron! Aaron!
请退后  女士
Please, step back, ma'am.
我知道他  我叫马里卢斯·圣地亚哥  艾伦
I know him. My name is Mariluz Santiago. Aaron!
艾伦
Aaron!
没事
It's okay.
你一人前来厄尔巴索吗  怎么不给我打电话
You came all the way to El Paso? Why didn't you just call me?
我不知道  也许我有些偏执
I don't know. Maybe I'm being paranoid, but--
对于什么很偏执
Paranoid about what?
一个记者一直在跟踪我
A reporter's been dogging me.
问我是什么身份地位  我来到美国的方式
Asking me questions about my status, about how I came to the United States,
以及你我的关系
about how you know me.
- 你怎么跟他说的  - 啥都没说  我一直在回避他
- What have you told him? -Nothing. I've been avoiding him.
很好  就这么做下去
Good. Just keep doing that.
他一直在威胁我  说他会向美国移民局举报我
He's been making these threats, saying he'll report me to ICE.
马里卢斯  没人会驱逐你
Mariluz, nobody's gonna deport you.
- 你怎么确定  - 因为我为总统工作
- How can you be sure? - I work for the president.
但如果你输了呢
But what if you lose?
好吧  听着  别跟任何人提起  可以吗
Okay, look, you gotta keep this to yourself, okay?
乔丹  好久不见
Jordan, long time.
嗨  马尔斯  都没怎么见到你
Oh, hey, Mars. Hardly see you around anymore.
因为选举那些事很忙
Oh, the election and all.
- 你会投我们一票  对吧  - 当然
- We can count on your vote, right? - Yeah, sure.
天哪  我起了这些恶心的疹子  可能是因压力太大
Man, I have this awful rash. Must be stress.
我发誓  我真想跳出这个躯壳
I swear, I feel like I just want to jump out of my skin.
听起来很糟糕
Sounds bad.
我在想拿一些你的东西
I was thinking about taking some of your stuff.
我想这是一个暗示
Well, I imagine this is just an inkling
与那些嗑药家伙的经历相比
compared to what those dope-sick folks experience, huh?
我听说这种渴望极其强烈  你无心顾及其他事
I heard that the cravings are so bad you can't even focus on anything else.
我是说在你试图做其他事的时候
I mean, you try to do something, anything,
就做一个三明治  付清账单  没有他们你根本做不好
just make a sandwich, pay some bills, and you just can't function without them.
一旦你尝到了甜头  你就会兴奋  渴望更多
And then once you get 'em, you're wired, and you just want more.
他妈的  真折磨人
Motherfuck! Must be excruciating.
你想要什么  哈珀
What do you want, Harper?
你一直是一个问题  现在你是一个解决方案
You've been part of the problem. Now, be part of the solution.
我不知道你在说啥  我们帮助人们缓解痛苦
I don't know what you're talking about. We help people manage their pain.
你想一个沿街毒贩一样掉他们上钩
You hook 'em like a dope dealer on the street.
好了  就这样
Okay, that's enough.
- 我还没说完  - 你他妈到底怎么回事儿
- No, I'm not finished. -What the fuck is wrong with you?
你为何不这么做  赎罪
Why don't you do this: make amends.
如果有人没有保险的话  免费把这个新药品给他们
If someone doesn't have insurance, give them this new drug of yours for free.
要是有保险的话  就把收入捐献给
Or if someone does, just donate the proceeds
节欲或减少危害计划
to abstinence or harm-reduction programs, yeah.
伙计  那根本不可能
That's not gonna happen, pal.
或许我能说服你
Maybe I'll be able to persuade you.
你正威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
我可没那么说
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
如果你问我的话  我会说我正在缓解自己的痛苦
No, if you ask me, I'd say I'm managing my pain.
我不知道你跟他们灌了什么迷魂汤
I don't know what the blue-fuck you told them,
但我们从所有国会黑人党团会议那
but we just got an official endorsement
获得了正式背书
from the entire Congressional Black Caucus.
好  现在我需要做的是向全国城市传达奇迹
Good. Now all I need to do is deliver a nationwide urban miracle.
别在我这儿
Not my station.
一些有望的民调结果刚出来
What is, some illuminating polling that just came in.
- 怎么样  - 棒极了
- How's it looking? - Amazing.
五个小时  我们已经筹措到了90万美元的善款
Five hours, and we've already raised almost $900,000.
在今天之内我们就能达到目标
We'll reach our goal by end of day.
不好意思  索尔先生  我们在总统办公室有事做
Excuse me, Mr. Shore, you're needed in the Oval.
好了  跟我来  一块儿做
Okay, you're coming with me. We did this together.
那我们就不推却了
If you insist.
他们因何而死
What killed them?
还在匡蒂科那分析着  但一些人死于出血性发烧
It's still being analyzed at Quantico, but some form of hemorrhagic fever.
基因武器
Genetically weaponized.
他们正在开发一种病毒  面向有色人种
They were developing a virus targeting people of color.
我想所有至上主义者都是白人
I assume all of these white supremacists were white.
或许这就是他们认为自己很安全的原因
Probably why they thought they were safe around it.
他们在接触了12小时内都死了
They were all dead within 12 hours of exposure.
如果这个一旦放出去了  必定会引起灾难性流行病
If this had gotten out, it would've been a catastrophic pandemic.
你应该为自己感到骄傲
You should be proud.
下一步是
What next?
这里是伊莱·梅斯医生
You've reached Dr. Eli Mays.
请留言  请记住  有人可能监听
Leave a message, bearing in mind someone may be listening.
嗨  是汉娜  他们要让我回分析部门
Hey, it's Hannah. They're moving me back to Analysis.
就这样
It's over.
所以我们现在的问题是他们出院的时间
So the question we have before us now is when they're released from the hospital,
艾莱纳一家怎么办
what do we do with the Orellana family?
我们可以把他们安置到避难所管道
We could put them in the asylum pipeline.
在过渡时期给予一些临时住所
Granting temporary residency in the interim.
你确定避难所是合法的吗
You sure the asylum claim is legitimate?
- 这很重要吗  - 当然了
- Does it matter? - Yes. Yes, it does.
这基本上可以让马泰奥成一个名流
This has practically made Mateo a celebrity.
他是绑架犯的首选目标
He's a clear target for kidnapping.
或者联合企业会从他的药物中偷得钱财
Yeah, or the cartels will steal the money for his medication.
- 我们还在考虑遣返吗  - 有这种可能
- Are we considering deportation here? - It's on the table.
我刚刚是进到了莫斯的竞选场地了吗
Did I just wander into the Moss campaign?
有一些来自佛罗里达大信息量的民调结果
Some informative polling from Florida.
每人都很高兴马泰奥有了肾  但是那的拉丁裔却想被遣返
Everyone's happy Mateo got his kidney, but the Latinos there favor deportation.
- 古巴人吗  - 不仅是古巴人
- Cubans? - Not only Cubans,
绝大多数也是波多黎各人
the majority of Puerto Rican voters, too.
拉丁裔选民不是很统一
The Latino electorate is not monolithic.
我们真的要按照民意做出决定吗
Are we really going to make a poll-driven decision here?
不是  如果你有危及生命的健康状况
No, we're not, but we're also not gonna be sending out a message
我们也不会散布消息
that if you have a life-threatening medical condition,
以及治理非法越境的问题
and manage to get across the border illegally,
这差不多是能永久居住的可行方案
that that's somehow a path to permanent residency.
他们的确违反了法律
They did break the law.
非法越境是一个行为不当的问题
Crossing the border illegally is a misdemeanor.
就好像他们超速奔去医院
It's like they went over the speed limit racing to the hospital.
更像是闯红灯  但我明白你的观点
More like running a red light, but I take your point.
你怎么看
What do you think?
我觉得赢不下佛罗里达州  我们就会失败
I think without Florida, we lose.
是啊
Yeah.
我想吃点烧烤或墨西哥美食
I'd like to try some barbecue or Mexican food,
反正就是巴黎没有的美食
something we can't get in Paris.
我知道有些地方有
I know a couple places.
你真是个好向导  谢谢
You have been an exceptional guide. Merci.
我认得你
I recognize you.
你好  你能帮我联系美国国会警察吗
Hello. Could you connect me to the Capitol Police?
你在这干嘛
What are you doing in here?
洗手
Washing my hands.
是  我在国会山的女卫生间  有一个男子在这
Yes, I'm in the Capitol ladies' room, and there's a man in here.
发生了什么  珊莎
What's going on, Sasha?
你的朋友进错了卫生间
Your friend is in the wrong restroom.
您说什么
I beg your pardon?
他没跟你说吗  他是一个装扮像女人的男人
Well, didn't he tell you? He's a guy posing as a woman.
珊莎  等等
Sasha, wait.
嗨  宝贝
Hey, sweetheart.
- 今天工作怎么样  - 很好
- How was work today? - Good.
我们可以调到你喜欢的那个恐怖真人秀
Why don't we put on that terrible reality show you love?
我没心情
I'm not really in the mood.
蒂娜  我好冷  能帮我拿件毛衣吗
Tina, I'm chilly. Could you grab my sweater?
当然  凯莉
Of course, Carrie.
明早我们在国家卫生研究所有预约
So we have an appointment at the NIH tomorrow morning.
宝贝  我不想这样
Oh, honey, I don't think so.
我们需要让你尽快开始这个协议
We need to get you started in this protocol as soon as possible.
告诉他们把我的位置转给别人吧
Tell them to give my spot to someone else.
什么  你在说啥
What? What are you talking about?
我无法再做更多治疗了
I can't go through any more treatment.
你可以  不然你就会死
Yes, you can. The alternative is death.
我在第四阶段
I'm Stage Four.
我已经接受现实了
I've made my peace with that.
妈  你来这我就能照顾好你
Mom, you came here so that I could take care of you
我需要你同意让我效劳
and I need you to let me do that.
宝贝  我来这儿不是想让你照顾我
Sweetheart, I didn't come here so you could take care of me.
我来这是因为协助自杀在华盛顿特区合法
I came here because assisted suicide is legal in DC.
晚上好  其实
Good evening. As you know,
由于柯克曼政府的干预
due to the intervention of the Kirkman administration,
马泰奥·奥瑞拉那已经接受了治疗  有挽救生命的意义
Mateo Orellana has received the lifesaving medical treatment
这是他来到美国的原因
for which he came to the United States.
奥瑞拉那一家表示对
The Orellana family extends their gratitude
美国民众表示感激  因为他们在这段困难时期一直在支持他们
to the American public for their support during this difficult time.
对于马泰奥的出院
Upon Mateo's discharge,
他们一家将会回到危地马拉
the Orellana family will return to Guatemala.
他的医生们与他家附近的医院协调好治疗事宜
His doctors will coordinate his care with a hospital near his home.
- 发生了什么  - 总统正在遣返他回国
- What happened? -POTUS is deporting him.
这是一个透明的动作  却在两方面都引起了愤世嫉俗的情绪
It's a transparent attempt to cynically have it both ways.
用贿赂迫使边境的人进入
Compel the transplant as a sop to the open borders crowd,
然后遣返这一家人以抚慰移民领头人
and then deport the family to placate immigration hardliners.
这不仅和政策没有太大关系  这也是政策上的失误
Not only is it incoherent as policy, it's also a wrongheaded political strategy
注定会让每个人不高兴  也会疏远每个人
doomed to not only please no one, but alienate everyone.
看吧  这就是持温和执政观点的问题
See, this is the problem running as a sensible centrist.
没有固定的信念和意识形态
With no fixed convictions or anchoring ideologies,
你的治理会变得毫无意义且即兴
you wind up with this nonsensical, improvisatory,
并有反效果
entirely contradictive governance.
美国人真的想要又一个为期四年绝望
Do the American people really want four more years
无方向的领导吗
of this hand-wringing, rudderless drift?
只是一个软弱的  摇摆不定的  无主见的  哈姆雷特式总统任期
This feckless, maybe-this, maybe-that, what-should-I-do, Hamlet presidency?
- 放松  - 伊莱  怎么回事  如果我身上有武器呢
- Easy. - Eli, what the hell? What if I was armed?
怎么了
What's wrong?
还没完
It's not over.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177